I had earlier made a free video on ICICI Lombard General Insurance Company and
told you about how the company is, how it
develops,
what returns can companies generate in the long term.
So, regarding the stock, we are seeing a big news coming
here and some
target price etc., fee structure, some
brokerage charges will be given to you here,
so
we will try to cover the numbers there in this video. It is a
small video, do not miss the video,
watch it completely, do not miss it even a little and
here I will try to explain to you
why you should buy ISRO. So first of all let us look at the
price of Lombard,
how much is its price, its price is 1242, right now it is
29 October 2020 at 12:15, when I am
making this video, maybe till then
you may see this price changing a little bit. As of
today, the stock
is up by almost 1% and it was listed on
September 2017 and from then till now,
if you see, the
stock here has earned a Julian Active
2%.  There was a
fall in the stock of Earn and Send here, but to stop this fall
here, it has recovered quite well and it has gone
up a little bit and whatever was left will go away in
time, that means
after some time, cover that too here and
give it to me, the rest can be yours separately, let's
talk about stop, you will see the stock of the well family being
created here, then see, the
brokers from a
big brokerage here, the name of Sher Khan, have kept
a target price here, they have kept the
target price of 1510 by clicking on it
here and these are from the side,
these are for the whole year, okay, so
here on 23 October 2030, this
target price has been kept here, now for a year,
this view has been kept in it
that the target of ₹15 to ₹10 will come here, you
will think that a stock of 1250 will be 1510, so what is the
return given in this, see
like 10, 20, 25 percent  There is a lot of profit
in the stock market if you
think about it, Mr. and Mrs. of Square Feet, who is the
world's biggest Mr.
and Mrs. One Butt Sir,
who is called the God of the stock market here,
he has said that if the
stock market shares get a clear signal
then it is very cold,
so here if you see its target of 1510,
if the stock achieves this target for a year then
it will give a very high
return, I will accept that keep your view
that you can even go up to 2000,
I will not call you wrong, but then there
is a lot of profit,
if you keep any stock and if it is not achieved then
you are the one who gets sad, look here
in the stock market, I mean if you
ask me, I do not expect
more than 20 percent in a year on any topic,
if it
comes more then that means a different thing, but the
expectation of more than 20 percent does
not last long in the stock market, Prasad Yadav should ask me, a
share of 20% is very high, if it
doubles the money in 5 years or four years, then that
26 processing is not less,
if you see here, they
kept a target of ₹1500 and see above this topic,
very soon you will see the stop coming in the decisions i.e.
in the futures market,
now you will be able to create this trick, there is a feature option here,
which was a news shot above,
so here due to this news, if
you see, the stock has also got some strength, the
rest of the staff has given a strong result, the result of
which for the quarter two, that is, the September quarter,
which came here, has given excellent and wonderful
results, so
I have made a jam on it whether you should buy the stock or not,
rest sir, stay connected with the channel from time
to time, you will get to know here which
stock to buy, when and
which stock will make a good amount of money for the long term,
but sir, if you see here, by
trading, by trading, by straight
trading, which is called trade, which is called straight,
sir, you can earn money, I mean, you can
earn thousands of rupees 2000 ₹5000 a day through your trading, but the person whom we call, the
money which is made in the long term  This is the
question, all this will
not happen through trading or click and keep it,
you will never forget it, you will never be able to
smoke, it will not happen, it will not happen, it will not happen, it will not happen, it will not happen, it will not happen, it will not happen, it will not happen, it will not happen, it will happen, it will happen, it will happen, it will happen, it will happen, it will happen, it will happen, it will happen, it will happen, it will happen, it will happen, it will happen, it will happen, it will happen, it will happen, it will happen, it will happen, it will happen, it will happen, it will happen, it will happen, it will happen, it will happen, it will happen, it will happen, it will happen, it will happen, it will happen, it will happen, it will happen, it will happen, it will happen, it will happen, it's a good thing ...
Regarding the episode number
123, I have made a complaint for the boys about the small things here in Boxer. I will do a
video call on Monday morning. I
request you to
definitely watch that video. Stay connected with Boxer Chawal from
time to time, that is,
with the market. If you want to connect, you do not have
much time etc., you are
not able to watch the market from time to time, then
stay connected with this channel. I try,
but even if any small
news comes here which can explain anything to you on your investment, that is, it can
leave an effect here, then I
make a video on it, I try to tell you,
till now it was like this and how did you like today's nature,
please tell me by commenting. If you have
any questions on this topic, then ask that too.
Otherwise, on which stock do you
want the next video here, you can also comment,
thank you. Jai Hans A